<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ShutUp!</string>

    <string name="double_wave">Double wave :</string>
    <string name="single_wave">Single wave or :\nFlip down</string>

    <string name="master_switch">Master switch\t</string>
    <string name="instructionstext">1. Single wave:\nwave over the proximity sensor (generally located near the front camera)
        to tell me what to do by selecting one of the functions from the list. Note that you can use anything to wave.
        A book will also work. You can also flip the phone down and the chosen function will be performed. Same will happen
        if you put phone on ear (useful during answer call)\n\n

        2. Double wave:\nwave over the proximity sensor two times
        consecutively with a time interval of less then 1.2 (by default) seconds to perform the selected function.\n\n

        3. Silent on pick up:\nthe phone will automatically silent when you pick it up from
        a flat surface. This will be ignored if the phone is already moving.\n\n

        4. Automatic speaker toggle:\nThe
        speaker phone will automatically turn on if the device is moved away from the ear. It will turn off if device is
        again brought back to the ear. It will only work after putting phone on ear at least once which, is to protect privacy.\n
        Note:\nThis does not work if headset is connected or audio is routed by bluetooth.
        So, I\'ve got you covered!\n\n

        5. Phone kept facing down:\nYou can end call or mute microphone during a call by putting phone on a flat
        surface facing down.\n\n

        Blacklist- You can blacklist contacts for which you do not want automatic speaker toggle to work.
        Thus, prevent embarrassing situations with sensitive contacts!\n\n

        Consecutive wave threshold- The time gap between two consecutive waves so that they are counted as double wave.
        </string>

    <string-array name="wavelistoptions">
        <item>Do nothing</item>
        <item>Silent phone</item>
        <item>End call</item>
        <item>Answer call</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="facedownlistoptions">
        <item>Do nothing</item>
        <item>End call</item>
        <item>Mute microphone</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="Settings_shortcutlongLabel">Open Settings in ShutUp!</string>

    <string name="Blacklist_title">Blacklist</string>
    <string name="Blacklist_shortcutlongLabel">Open Blacklist for automatic speaker on/off</string>
</resources>
